This program contains graphic content, adult themes and violence that may not be suitable for some viewers and is inappropriate for children.
This content is entirely fictional.  The content is intended for mature audiences only.
Hey! You okay, Oliver?! Hang in th--!
That's the last of the pursuers, Levi.
Everyone got turned into Titans
and only you survived.
Probably for the same reason you're not
dead yet: because you're an Ackermann.
But what to do now?
We can't stop Zeke anymore, so it's
up to Armin or Commander Pyxis.
Even supposing that Eren
does betray Zeke,
if the Jaegerists control
the island with spinal fluid,
we'll be fugitives
for the rest of our lives.
Looks like my turn has come...
Even if I thought I did the right thing.
Times change and you end up in a cell.
What do you say we live out
here forever? Huh, Levi?
That was...! No way...! Eren's gonna...?!
Levi!
The Beast... Where'd that shithead go?
Lie back down.
It's been half a day since Zeke
and the Jaegerists left for Shiganshina.
What happened?
I botched it. He was fully prepared
to die... and I didn't see it.
He got away again.
That's unfortunate, but right now--
If we run and hide, what will be left?
Wha--? I guess you overheard
me talking to myself.
What... are you building? You gonna
pull me on that... with a horse?
There's no way in hell you can
stay out of the action.
Yeah, you're right. I can't.
My goal... is to kill Zeke.
Looks like our interests align,
Theo Magath... Pieck Finger.
Levi Ackermann. It seems you can
stand up to one of the Nine, but...
How do you plan on
dodging a bullet like that?
I can't dodge a bullet, but I've
come before you in this sad state.
Whether you shoot or listen is up to you.
Then I'll ask this first: You say you'll
kill Zeke, but where is he now?
Zeke's probably being held by Eren
to make use of his royal blood.
No, by the Founding Titan.
It seems the Titan expert Hange knows
everything--even more than Marley.
Have you seen the Founding Titan?
I know it's so humongous that it
seems like nothing can be done, so...
We've got no other choice.
We've gotta put our powers together.
"Pride"
How exactly do I get my mom to
eat Falco? Just do it by force?
If he's hurt and finds out about
his Titan powers, it's over.
I can't afford to fail.
I've gotta think of a better way.
What an innocent kid.
He hasn't whined once about camping
out here with every reason to doubt me.
Does he seriously trust me?
Dammit! Sasha...
Would you have understood?
Um, I thought we were going to
a hospital, not a deserted village.
Yeah. There's something
interesting here I wanna show you.
This... is Ragako Village!
Eh?
How do you... know that?
Last night, I heard you
talking to yourself.
Sasha was your comrade shot by
Gabi on the airship, wasn't she?
You brought me here knowing
who I was but pretending not to.
Why? To get revenge... on me?
No. Stuff like that happens
in the heat of battle.
Don't worry, it can't move.
It's been like this for years.
What... were you gonna do...
after showing me this?
Can you help me brush the Titan's teeth?
You don't get a chance
like this every day.
Huh?
We've gotta go way up there to brush.
Let's climb up and take a look.
Sounds good, right?
Right...
Falco! Get away from him!
Gabi?!
He's gonna feed you to the Titan!
Huh?!
Conny! Stop!
Stay back! Don't come near us!
Conny!
Shuddap! I don't wanna hear it!
Don't talk! You wouldn't get it!
You're just gonna say to give up
on my mom and let him live!
A know-it-all wouldn't
get how idiots work!
Falco! Use the Jaw's power!
The Jaw's power? Huh?
What about Galliard?
You can't...! Stop! Falco!
Gabi, please forgive Conny.
Huh?
Hey! I said to stay back!
Hey! What are you doing?!
Say something, Armin!
You told me not to talk!
So... I'll let my actions talk.
My brother...
What was your plan if I hadn't saved you?
To turn your mom back into a human.
And inherit the Colossal Titan.
If you thought for a second,
you know that'd only make her suffer.
When my mom sent me off,
she said to be a splendid soldier.
And yet, her son almost
killed a kid and a friend.
That's the kind of soldier I am.
Me, too. I couldn't stack
up to the commander.
Armin... I wanna be a soldier
my mom could take pride in.
So, let's go save people in trouble.
"Information Available for Public Disclosure"
"Ragako Village"
"A village that was deserted after being overrun by Titans. Upon their arrival, the Scouts discovered a single Titan with extremely small limbs which made it unable to move. Later, when Titans were being eradicated from the island, former Ragako resident Conny Springer
requested for the village to become
a 'Titan Observation Zone' and be left as-is."
I found you.
I'm glad.
Did you come looking for me?
Or... for this scarf?
I knew you would have it.
I'm sorry. I thought it'd
bring me closer to you.
I have Thunder Spear shrapnel
in me that they can't remove.
It's a pity I won't be able to see the
free world that Eren Jaeger creates.
It wasn't much, but I had the chance
to speak with him... about you.
He talked about wanting
to throw the scarf out.
So, rather than throw it out,
I thought I'd just...
Give it back.
I became a soldier because I admired you.
I have no regrets.
Because I gave my heart and my life
following in your footsteps.
Is that the last of the rumbling Titans?
Finally, an end to all this noise.
To me, it sounds like
the bells of freedom.
Our Eldian Empire has endured the
world's persecution for 100 years!
That ends now! Now, we are free!
Our liberator, Eren, and we Jaegerists
have triumphed over the world!
Say, Mikasa. Will you join the
Jaegerists and rule as one of 'em?
Not interested.
Looks like Jean made up his mind.
Give your hearts!
--Give your hearts!
Long live the Jaegerists!
Give your hearts!
This one's for Eren!
We should hurry and see Reiner.
It's okay, he'll be out for days.
Is this detour a good idea?
We've gotta fill our stomachs.
You think it's true, Armin?
Mmm. If all hardening has come
undone, it's likely that Annie has--
A-Annie?!
--Huh?
--Eh?
Huh?
Annie's stuffing her face with pie!
Cut it out, Conny.
She eats like a pig!
It's her first pie in years!
Sorry! The line took forever and--
She's gone.
"Dear Hitch. I ran into Armin and Conny
and decided to join them.
I'm going ahead. Sorry for the trouble.
Thanks for talking to me these
past four years. Goodbye.
Your gloomy roommate."
Good grief. I can't finish this alone.
Comrades of the Empire,
thank you for gathering!
We will now execute two Volunteers
who opposed the Eldian Empire!
With this, we shall carry on Eren's
will to dominate the world...
...by declaring our reign
over Paradis Island!
This criminal is Yelena!
The real reason she rebelled from Marley
and supported the Eldian Empire
was so Zeke could obtain
the Founding Titan's power
and wipe out Eldians with
their euthanization plan!
--In the end, she's a filthy Marleyan!
--Yeah!
Eren managed to beat
Zeke and halt the plan,
but this criminal served
as Zeke's loyal pawn!
You whore!
Send her to hell!
Yelena... Have any last words?
Aren't you gonna shoot?
Die, mainlander!
The Subjects of Ymir will prevail!
Ymir's bloodline will last forever!
Shoot her! Shoot her!
Shoot her! Shoot her...!
Not yet!
This criminal is Onyankopon.
He aided Eldia without knowing of
the euthanization plan, however...!
He said he'd rather die than
live under the Eldian Empire!
It's not too late to change your mind--
I aided Eldia to save my homeland from
Marley, but I was helping you, too!
And what did that get me?
My homeland will be crushed
and my family massacred!
And the only ones left will
be you xenophobic shits?
Sucking up to you guys
for life isn't worth it!
Even you should know how
insane indiscriminate killing is!
Why don't any of you understand?!
Don't just stand there!
Say something, Jean!
Huh? Hey!
Whoops. I missed.
Hey, what's the big idea?
Floch!
It's the Cart Titan!
--They got away!
--Jean got eaten!
--And Yelena!
Shit! Where's Mikasa?!
Have her... go after...!
Where... is Mikasa?
Hear that?
Four gunshots in a row--
Jean's signal to continue the plan.
We've got enough weapons and food!
All their eyes will be on the
other side of the fort. Let's go!
Someone's watching us!
What now, Armin?
Gotta keep going! Hurry, Mikasa!
I ain't ever going in a
Titan's mouth again!
The Cart can stay a Titan for months,
right? Don't you brush your teeth?
That's a rude thing to ask a lady.
When did you partner with Marley?
Last night.
Why? If you stayed a Jaegerist,
you'd have everything you wanted.
I wish I could've plugged my ears
and stayed cooped up in that room.
But then, those ashy bones
would never forgive me.
Jean... I don't quite follow, but thanks.
Just wash off already.
Why... me?
Securing you was part of the deal
for us to borrow the Cart's power.
They wanted you alive.
Get up.
Annie!
Calm down, Reiner!
Don't worry! They're our allies!
There's not much time. Let's go.
Where to?
To save the world.
Enemies are made in the chaos of war.
We hated, loathed, and killed one another.
What lies beyond the campfire?
Next episode: "Night of the End."
"Night of the End"